I heard
you arrested the palace painter,
Chu Qingyun, General.
To think he is a Northern spy.
You are truly well-informed, Duke.
Indeed.
I did find a peculiar painting
on Chu Qingyun.
It bears the emblem of an enemy spy ring.
I actually buy his paintings quite often.
What does this emblem you speak of
look like, General?
Some things are better left unasked,
Duke.
How do you plan
to deal with Chu Qingyun, General?
I have tortured him
into confessing,
and he awaits execution in autumn.
Then this treason case will be closed.
There is no end to catching spies anyway.
I cannot waste all my time
on them.
Don't you agree,
Duke?
It seems Ning Yuanci
is really going to make a ruthless move
against Chu Qingyun.
And Xue Ruowan really
doesn't care about
Chu Qingyun's life or death at all.
You guys get to play both the heroes
and the villains.
I work so hard
saving this one and that one,
only to end up being the sucker.
It's all because of
this damn script system.
I don't even know
how to act anymore.
I just want to say,
what gives you the right
to represent the audience?
Why do I have to be at your mercy
just to survive?
Does this world really have to be
full of fighting and killing?
Can't there be a little truth,
goodness, and beauty?
Forget it.
If I change the main plot
and character settings without permission,
Xue Ruowan will be in danger.
But Chu Qingyun is the male lead.
If Ning Yuanci kills him,
I won't be able to
clear the game and reach the finale.
How can I make Ning Yuanci change his mind
without breaking
my evil woman persona?
I'll wait for you at Fengya Pavilion
in Wangyue Tower tomorrow night.
Brother Ning,
I knew you would come.
No matter how willful I am
or how much I anger you,
you still care about me,
right?
Didn't you say
your feelings for me were fake
and just an act?
What does it matter
if it's an act or not?
After all,
we are the same kind of people,
aren't we?
Why exactly did you ask me
to come here today?
Tomorrow
is your wedding night
with Xue Ruowan.
Of course I have to have you
before she does.
Isn't it a bit late
to try and please me now?
I said those things out of anger.
Xue Ruowan and Chu Qingyun
are in love.
Instead of letting them be,
you hold on to Chu Qingyun.
I thought
you had actually fallen for
Xue Ruowan.
So,
you're jealous.
I'm looking at the big picture.
It's fine if you marry Xue Ruowan.
But you must promise me
you won't touch her.
And it'd be best if you let Chu Qingyun
go,
so they can be together.
That's the only way to prove
you love me,
not her.
What if
I refuse?
Then I'll just have to drag you
to hell with me.
You want to kill me.
Just kidding.
In terms of martial arts,
how could I ever defeat Ning?
But what you didn't expect is that
I applied my mother's secret poison
on my lips.
If you don't want to die
from the poison with me tonight,
agree to my terms.
You just said
we are the same kind of people.
So it takes no effort
for me to see right through you.
Are you crazy?
Ning Yuanci,
didn't I tell you that
when you kill someone,
the heart is right here?
You want to be ruthless
but you can't bring yourself to do it.
You can't play the villain well.
Who wants to compete in acting with you?
You're so badly hurt.
Let's go find a doctor.
Don't actually die.
I've suffered this kind of injury
countless times on the battlefield.
I won't die.
But you,
don't get involved in things
you shouldn't.
Otherwise,
for the crimes of assassinating
the Defender General
and colluding with spies,
your Xue family couldn't pay for it
even if they died ten thousand times.
Strange.
Where is my bottle of Heartbreak Powder?
Oh no.
Could Ying'er have taken it
to deal with Xue Ruowan?
Mother. Ying'er.
There, there.
Don't cry.
Let me see.
A-Are
you hurt anywhere?
Let me see.
What happened?
What should I do?
Don't be afraid.
Even if you killed Xue Ruowan,
I would take the blame for you.
Actually, it's not Xue Ruowan.
She is perfectly fine.
W-
Weren't
you going to poison that good-for-nothing
Xue Ruowan?
I didn't even get to
use this Heartbreak Powder.
Wan'er, you are truly
as beautiful as a fairy.
Only you are worthy of
this imperially bestowed wedding dress.
Your daughter is getting married today.
I bid farewell to you, Father.
I know I owe you a lot.
You lost your mother at a young age
and suffered a lot.
But you have always been
the most obedient and sensible one.
I am very gratified
that you agreed to this marriage.
Father, you don't have
to pretend to be guilty
and say these things.
In the end,
it's just that you don't love me enough.
If you have to choose a daughter
to push into the fire pit,
it can only be me.
Do you want your sister
to go to her death?
Did you think
the assassins at the mansion
and your poisoning
were accidents?
It was all planned by Ning Yuanci.
He just wanted to frame me
for colluding with the Northern Frontier,
and then bring down our Xue family
in the name of eliminating spies.
If your sister hadn't accidentally
ruined his plan,
I would have been burdened with those
unwarranted charges long ago.
Then why did you still make me marry him?
Ning Yuanci is the Emperor's adopted son
and confidant.
Breaking the engagement
means disobeying His Majesty.
He wants you to marry him
just to have another hostage
in his hands.
Am I supposed to just sit
and wait for death?
I must take the initiative.
So,
Father, you mean to use me?
Ying'er is pure-hearted
and deeply in love with Ning Yuanci.
She can't be ruthless.
But you can.
I am unfortunate
to have no sons.
I only have you two daughters.
Although I can't
treat you both equally,
I promise you...
I will do my best to keep you safe.
As we discussed,
poison Ning Yuanci on the wedding night.
I will send someone to coordinate with you
and help you fake your death to escape.